I hate this place.
我厌恶这个地方
Water?
是水？
Water.
水
Water!
水！
Now that is sick.
真是令人感到恶心
- Are you watching this? - No, Thanks. I don't look any more.
- 这个你看了没有？ - 不 我不想再看了
We've seen a lot of... But this is just...
我们看了不少了    但
Oh, dear God!
噢 我的天！
Wow...
哇
You know you shouldn't be looking at the files.
你应该明白你不该看这些文件的
- It's not against the rules. - But it's not encouraged.
- 这又没有违反规定 - 但是不提倡这么错
- Come on man, we've all... - It's not encouraged.
- 行了 老兄 我们已经    - 这种事我们不提倡
Okay.
好吧
Okay, screw this.
好的 看这招
- Pawn to King 2. - Knight to Queen's Bishop 6.
- 帅2进卒 - 皇后移6 将军
- Check. - What?
- 就这样走 - 什么？
I didn't even see that.
我都没看
I was just wondering... When is Chickliss coming back?
我只是想知道    查克斯什么时候回来？
Some time this week. Probably all suntanned, the prick.
也许这周 或许他已经被晒黑了
Let's see...
让我想想看
King to King's Bishop 8.
帅进相移8
Rook takes Queen. Check.
车吃皇后 将军
Dammit.
该死的
Damn!
完了！
- Sorry. - Shut up I don't need your sympathy.
- 不好意思 - 闭嘴 我不用你同情
And Owen?
还有欧文呢？
- Where is Owen? - You're trying to psych me out or what?
- 欧文去哪里了？ - 你是不是故意扰乱我的思维？
I can't hear myself think.
我的思路全被你打断了
Owen is...
欧文
Owen is probably out sick again. That would be my best guess.
欧文肯定是又出去吐了 我可以肯定
You sure?
你确定？
Yes.
是的
Yes!
太棒了！
Despite your rather transparent tactics, Brainman, prepare to die.
尽管你的战术很精明 但是 聪明人准备受死吧
Bishop to Queen's Knight 7. Checkski!
主教移7至皇后 将军！
Queen takes Bishop. I believe that's Checkski-Mateski.
皇后吃主教 我想这样就平局了
What? No way.
什么？没门
Ah come on, how did you...?
过来 你是如何   ？
You freak of nature!
你这天生的怪物！
You know the other night I heard some noise.
你知道吗？ 这两天我半夜听到一些声响
- Noise? - Yeah.
- 声音？ - 是的
In Owen's room, like a... like a scuffle.
就在欧文的房间 好像是    在进行混战
- Really? - Yeah.
- 真的？ - 是的
- You don't think that...? - You dreamt it.
- 你不认为那应该是   ？ - 你是在做梦吧？
- No, look... - You dreamt it.
- 不是的 你听着    - 你在做梦
You're always complaining about your nightmares.
你总是抱怨你做的那些恶梦
They come for you at night.
他们晚上会来找你的
What?
什么？
- They come for you at night. - Who does?
- 他们晚上会来找你的 - 是谁？
They do.
就是他们
- Drop it. - They do.
- 够了 - 就是他们了
Enough!
我说够了！
What are you suicidal?
你想自取灭亡吗？
Good. They didn't forget lunch this time.
还好 还没有忘了给我们送午饭
Goat cheese salad with ginseng,
羊奶酪拌人参色拉
liver fricasée and mango sorbet. Eeewh.
猪肝和芒果雪糕
Must be you.
是你的
Steak frites. That's me.
烤牛排 这是我的
Hey!
嗨！
Wha..? Oh! Sorry.
怎么了？ 哦！对不起
Bless us our Lord for these thy gifts which we're about to receive,
感谢主赐予我们的食物
from thy bounty through you, Lord. Amen.
感谢主的仁慈 阿门
Amen.
阿门
Down the hatch.
可以吃了
"Please record REMsleeper in room 17 24 09".
"请记录17 24 09房间的REM参与者"
Let's go.
开始吧
Okay. Zooming out of 06, 12, 21.
好的 缩小06  12  21
And zooming in to 17, 24, 9.
然后放大17  24  9
Here we go. Hot-patching gear works
我们开始了 开动热力齿轮
and flipping to REM reader mode.
调整为读取REM的模式
Locating subject. Subject located.
查找目标 目标锁定
Zooming in.
放大
Wow...
哇
Keep your tongue in your mouth, Brainman. We're on the clock.
闭上你的嘴 时间紧迫
Are we locked?
锁定了吗？
Sorry. Locked on.
对不起 已经锁定
Thank you. Arm extension, Go.
谢谢 机械装置启动 开始
Calibrating...
校准
- Steady. - I got it, I got it.
- 固定 - 没问题 完成了
Light her up.
让他醒过来
Interscan is locked. Commencing REM read.
内部扫描锁定 开始读取REM
Mommy!
妈咪！
Mommy Help!
妈咪 救命！
Anna!
安娜！
No! No!
不！不要！
Anna!
安娜！
Okay. Now let's cycle back.
好的 现在我们倒回去
And there you have it.
就是这样
If you do this long enough, you can do it in your sleep.
如果做这个做足够久  睡觉的时候都能做
In your sleep...
睡觉的时候
Recording dreams in your sleep. That's funny.
记录你做的梦 好玩吧
When's the last time you remember being outside?
你还记得你最后一次出去是什么时候吗？
Last night. I had a dream of being at the beach.
昨晚 我做梦到自己在海边
No, I mean really outside, not a dream.
不 我是说真的出去  不是在做梦
I... I don't remember.
我    我是不记得了
I've been busy lately.
最近我比较忙
Overloaded, actually. Picking up slack.
超负荷的 事实上
For you, I might add.
很想放松下 为了你 我还是可以的
I don't remember either.
我也不记得了
- Isn't that weird? - You're weird.
- 奇怪吗？ - 你确实很奇怪
Shut up and let me concentrate.
闭嘴 让我集中精神
Dammit!
该死的！
- You know, I was just thinking... - Stop thinking.
- 你知道 我只是在想    - 不要再想了
- What's gotten into you? - What's gotten into me?
- 你到底怎么了？ - 我怎么了？
- You know who these are? - They're Chickliss' kids.
- 你知道这是谁？ - 他们是查克斯的孩子
- Arthur and Sunshine. - Orphans. They're orphans.
- 亚瑟和珊珊 - 孤儿 他们是孤儿
You told me Chickliss was on vacation.
你告诉我查克斯在休假
I have to go to the can.
我不得不隐瞒着
Try not to drool on the controls. It screws up the calibration.
不要设法将梦话变成现实 这是有距离的
Bastards.
混帐
Where is she?
她(安娜)在那里？
What have you done with her?
你们对她做了什么？
Where is...?
哪里   ？
What have you done to me?
你们对我做了什么？
I can't remember...
我记不起...
Why can't I remember my daughter's name?
为什么我记不起我女儿的名字了？
Hey!
嗨！
Let me go!
放开我！
- Get off me! - Okay. Okay. Sorry.
- 离我远点！ - 好的 好的 对不起
It's okay.
没事了
She's one of us.
她是我们的一份子
Touch me again, soldier, and you'll be eating your eyeballs.
再碰我 大兵  我会把你的眼珠吃了
Why soldier? What do you know about me?
大兵？ 你怎么知道我？
Tattoo, on you forehead. You're on the squad, right killer?
你额头上的纹身？ 你正在当班 不是吗 杀人犯？
You show up by night and people disappear.
夜里你就会现出原形 杀掉所人
- Why did you do that? - Because you're scum.
- 你为什么这么做？ - 因为你是人渣
Look miss, you have a certain disadvantage here.
听着小姐  你现在出一个困境当中了
None of us remembers how we got here, or pretty much anything else.
我们都不知道是怎么来的  或者其他相关的事
Including who we are, so whatever you think you know about me,
包括我们自己是谁  所以不管你知道任何关于我的事
I don't even know myself.
我还是想不起自己是谁
I don't trust her. She knows something.
我不相信她 她还记得某些事
Thank God somebody does.
感谢老天终于有人记得
Have you seen any children? A little girl?
你们看一个孩子了吗？ 一个小女孩？
No.
没有
My God. I hope they don't put kids in here.
我的天 我希望他们不要连孩子也放进来
- That would be horrible. - What if they drop children in here?
- 那太恐怖了 - 他们应该不会把孩子放到这
I gotta keep moving.
我必须走了
Wait! you gotta be careful climbing around here.
等等！　在这周围爬动要小心点
- Why? - There are traps.
- 为什么？ - 这里有陷阱
Traps? How do you know?
陷阱？ 你怎么知道？
Because of this.
你可以看看这个
That's good bandage. Are you a doctor?
绷带缠的还不错  你是医生？
- I don't know. - I did it.
- 我不知道 - 我绑的
I may be freakin' Mother Teresa for all I know, But I don't remember.
我可能是特里萨修女  但是我不记得了
You remember something.
你记得
Before all of this.
在这之前的事
Not much.
但是不多
Being chased through the woods, by guys like you.
记得被像你这样的人  在树林里追杀我
The tattoo set me off.
是那个纹身让我想起来的
When I first woke up, I don't think I would have known my own name
当我醒来  我不认为我们需要知道自己的名字
if it wasn't stitched on my shirt.
如果它们缝在我们的衣服上
I don't even know if this is my name.
我不知道这是否是自己的名字
I feel like we've been here for hours and I still can't remember anything!
我感觉我们来这有几个小时了 而且什么都不记得了！
Give her a moment...
让他冷静一下
Fine. A moment.
好吧 就一会儿
We gotta get moving while we still have our strength.
趁我们还有力气的时候 我们最好采取点行动
You guys have a plan?
你有计划了？
We keep moving in the same direction until we find the edge.
我们朝一个方向一直走 直到找到尽头
This place has got to end eventually.
这个地方总会有个终点的
What about the traps?
那些陷阱怎么办？
We test the rooms. We have a system.
我们只能一个个探测 我们会有方法的
It's safe!
这里安全！
I'm going in!
我进去了！
Help!
救命！
What kind of animals would do this?!
是什么禽兽做的？！
Does she look familiar to you?
她和你很像？
I keep thinking I've seen her before...
我在想我以前好像见过她
- I wonder what she's in for. - You're making a mistake.
- 我想知道她到底是谁？ - 那是你的错觉
Huh?
嗯？
What the first rule I taught you about this job?
这个工作的首要规则 我应该跟你讲过吧？
- Neatness counts? - Very funny.
- 准确记录？ - 可笑
Don't get involved.
不要自己陷进去
I know, I'm not getting involved OK? I'm drawing.
我知道 我没有陷入进去 我在画画
You have your chess, Owen has his fish, Chickliss...
你有你的国际象棋  欧文有他的鱼 查克斯
Can we spend 5 minutes without bringing up Owen and Chickliss please?
我们不要再提欧文和查克斯好不好  就5分钟也可以？
And get us back on real-time. You're gonna get us in trouble.
我们还是回到现实中吧 你让我们陷入困境
I'll show you three ways to beat that game if you answer one question.
我可以告诉3种赢棋的方法 如果你回答我一个问题
- Fine. What? - Okay, what I wanna know...
- 好的 什么？ - 好 我想要知道
Hold it. Show me.
等等 你先下给我我看看
Okay.
好吧
Check Mate.
将军
You win.
你赢了
That's brilliant. Do that again.
太聪明了 再来一遍
- What do you know about a third exit? - What?
- 你知道还有第三个出口吗？ - 什么？
A third exit.
第三个出口
An auxiliary exit that leads directly outside.
辅助出口可以直接出去
- There's no such thing. - Owen said there was.
- 没听说过这种事 - 欧文说有
- He said Chickliss found more plans... - They were having you on.
- 他说查克斯找到更多的    - 你当时在干什么
No way. I think that that's why they're gone. I think they've found something...
事实上 我认为那是他们为什么走了的原因 我想他们找到了
I think you'd better stop listening to old wives' tales.
我想你最好不要再去听那些荒诞的事
- Listen to me. - This conversation in over.
- 听我说    - 谈话到此结束
- Don't you ever worry? - About what?
- 难道你不担心吗？ - 担心什么？
One day, you're gonna wake up inside.
有一天 当你醒来的时候自己也在里面
The only way I'm gonna wake up inside, is if I keep on talking to you.
如果我和你谈的太多了 我就有可能进去
No.
不
These things are useless!
这些东西完全没有用！
The sensors there must've been different. Maybe they're not motion sensors.
这里的传感器应该不完全相同 也许这些不是动作传感器
Maybe they're triggered by heat, or sound, or something...!
可能它们是靠热感应的  或者声音 或者其他什么   ！
Why don't you just admit it? We're dead!
你就不能承认自己不行吗？ 我们就要死了！
He can't admit it. It's the training.
他不能这样 这是他们训练的结果
- The army never admits defeat. - You got a problem with me lady?
- 军队不能承认失败 - 女士 你对我有意见吗？
- Yeah. - Why?
- 是的  - 为什么？
I don't trust you.
我不信任你
- Oh, how the hell did we miss this? - What is it?
- 噢 妈的 我们怎么没发现这个？ - 是什么东西？
C-I-A.
C-I-A
What is that? Clues to who built this place?
这是什么意思？ 暗示是谁建的这个地方？
I think that's just a coincidence. Try the other doors.
我觉得这应该有一定的悬机 试试其他几个门
Y-Y-O.
Y-Y-O
U-D-S.
U-D-S
S-A-N.
S-A-N
What do they mean?
这是什么意思？
I think it's a mistake to think of these letters as meaning something.
我想如果认为这些字母组合 是某些单词 那就错了
It's like some kind of code or puzzle we have to figure out.
它们像是密码或字谜什么的 我们得知道它的含意
A puzzle? They're playing with us!
字谜？ 他们在耍我们！
- We should make a map. - Using what?
- 我们得画个地图． - 用什么？
- Our blood? - I don't know.
- 我们的鞋子？ - 我也不知道
Maybe. You got a better idea?
也许 好像听起来是个好主意？
I have a better idea.
我有办法了
I need something. I need...
我还需要点东西 我要
Your hair pin.
你的发针
They did us the favour of polishing our boots.
这些擦亮了的靴子 就是他们给我们的最好的工具
Okay, We'll find the safe rooms.
好了  我们找出安全的房间
C-I-A. Give me the others.
C-I-A 把其他几个告诉我
Y-Y-O U-D-S
Y-Y-O, U-D-S
And S-A-N.
And S-A-N
- Good memory. - Yeah, in the short term.
- 记性不错 - 是的 短时间的可以
Now I wish I could remember what happened to me between birth and about 3 hours ago.
现在我希望我能记起 我出生后到来这里3个小时之前事
Right.
呵
I dunno...
我不知道
Shoe polish and a hair pin.
鞋油和发针
Nothing in this place is random.
他们居然没想到
Maybe the bastards just underestimated us.
可能是那些混蛋小瞧我们了
So near and yet so far.
远在天边 近在眼前
Yeah, but she's doing better than most.
没错  但是她是那一群人中做得最好的了
I mean half of them don't even notice the letters, Let alone map them.
我是说有一半以上的人没有 注意到那些字母 没想到地图的做法
I meant the chess.
我在是说棋局呢
Give it up. She doesn't stand a chance.
放弃吧 她不会有任何机会的
Of course she has a chance.
她肯定有希望的
Yeah? You're gonna ride in on your white horse and whisk her out?
是吗？ 你难道想当白马王子 然后把她救出去？
The rooms can realign to zero position.
房间会排列到起始位置
No it happens, and then she'll figure out the letters and uhh... sail through.
如果这样 她又知道了字母的含义    就可以很轻松出来了
And what's the first thing the program does when the rooms realign to zero position?
但是什么才能使系统把房间 排列到起始位置？
- Clean sweep. - Exactly.
- 擦掉 - 准确来说
The only thing that's gonna sail through that is their ashes.
能顺利出来的东西 那就是他们的骨灰
Cheer up buddy. You'll catch you another one.
开心点 伙计 也没有那么糟糕
The boys upstairs like 'em young and pretty.
这样他们至少可以永葆青春
Don't you ever feel guilty?
你从没感到过内疚吗？
- Don't you ever feel? - Son, you're outta line.
- 从没有过吗？ - 孩子 不应该这样说
- Yeah whatever... - Excuse me?
- 但是 无论如何    - 你到底在干嘛？
Why don't you stop your doodling and do some work for a change?
你为什么不停下你手中的烂画 换点其他的事做？
Like what?
比如？
We're waiting for orders, it's what we do best. It's what we do.
我们在等待命令 我也只能做这个 不然还能干什么？
Clean up your space. It's disgraceful.
把你的四周打扫一下 太脏了
- You're kidding, right? - Do I look like I'm kidding?
- 你在开玩笑？ - 我像是在开玩笑？
This one's S-D-F.
这边是 S-D-F
Wait a minute.
等一下
- What? - I don't know if this makes any difference,
- 什么？ - 我不知道这个是不是有什么不同
But they're not periods, They're commas.
但是它们没有规律  这些点号
He's right. They're commas.
他说的没错 就是这些点号
Okay, so they're commas. What difference does it make?
好的 就算他们是点号 那有什么不同吗？
We don't even know what the letters mean yet.
我们根本不懂得这些字母的含义
I mean if they were numbers, I'd understand the commas.
我是想说如果它们是数字  我就知道这些点号的含意了
Understand the commas how?
这些点号要怎么看出来？
Well isn't that how you plot coordinates on a graph?
你为什么不在图表上画一下坐标？
X coordinate, comma, Y coordinate, comma, Z coordinate.
X坐标 逗点  Y坐标 点号 Z坐标
Right. So if the rooms were labelled with numbers,
没错 如果房间用数字贴上标签
like "10,1,7", you'd know something about the room's position.
像"10 1 7" 你就知道房间的坐标了
Yeah but we've got letters that so far tell us absolutely nothing.
但是我们只是知道些字母 这些是不够的
That's where you're wrong, soldier.
大兵 你错了
The letters tell us one important fact the number never would.
字母暗示着一件很重要的事实 但是仅仅数字得话就不行
- What fact? - There are only 26 letters in the English alphabet.
- 什么事实？ - 英文字母表有26个字母
So?
那么？
So we know the parameters.
那么我们就知道参数了
Exactly. If each room has its own unique letter combination,
其实 如果每个房间都有他唯一 的字母组合
Then it's a pretty good bet that this whole place is a cube
我敢肯定 所有的房间在一个立方体里
with 26 rooms on each side.
每一边有26个房间
Worst case scenario, we're anywhere from
现在最糟糕的是  我们只是在
1 to 25 rooms away from the edge.
位于边缘的1-25个房间中的一个
- Let's go! - Great!
- 我们走吧！ - 太好了！
Actually, it's your turn to go first.
好啊 那你第一个上
S-O-S. No kidding.
S-O-S 别开玩笑
Ahh.. Guess we'll try another way.
哦   伙计们或许应该走另外条路
Rains, Rains, Rains, Rains...
蕾斯  蕾斯  蕾斯  蕾斯
Cassandra.
卡桑德拉
The little girl's name is Anna.
那个小女孩的名字叫安娜
Protests and strikes. Troublemakers up north.
抗议和罢工 暴动者都来自北部
The whole country's going to crap.
整个国家乱七八糟
Ungrateful pigs.
该死的猪
Oh my God, Oh my God...
噢 我的天  我的天
What is it now?
怎么了？
Please tell me that's not... Would you put that away?
不要告诉那是    你就不能把它放下来吗？
There's no consent form.
这没有协议书
- What? - There is not pink page, the consent form is missing!
- 什么？ - 那粉红色的协议书不见了！
- So? - So?!
- 那么？ - 那就意味着？！
You know the rules. She can't be in there without a consent form!
你应该懂得规定的 如果没有协议书她就不应该在那里！
You think they're gonna stop this whole operation because you lost a piece of paper?
你认为他们会停止整个运行 就因为不见了一张纸？
I didn't lose it.
不是因为我们丢掉
Look you know how anal these guys are.
你看上面  你知道这些人有多么可悲吗？
- Maybe she'll get another hearing. - Listen to yourself!
- 可能她会去控告 - 一边去吧你！
But this could be huge! A mistrial!
这是会很严重的！
- Oh sure, anything you say. - Look...
- 是的 你说的没错 - 听着
See? Told you I recognized her.
看到了？ 告诉你我已经知道她是谁了
"Opposition Leaders Stage Illegal Strike"
"反对派举行非法罢工"
She's a political. So that would explain it.
她是个政客 所以这个可以解释这一切
What do you mean?
什么意思？
I mean, there might not be a consent form.
我是想说 这可能根本就没有协议书
Get it?
懂吗？
But that's illegal.
但是那是非法的
You know for a child prodigy, you ain't too bright.
我知道你是个天才  但是你不能太聪明了
- We gotta do something. - Like what?
- 我们应该做点什么 - 做什么？
- We gotta let 'em know upstairs. - And how are we gonna do that?
- 我们应该叫上面的人知道  - 那我们应该怎么做？
Call up.
打电话
- It's just for emergencies. - Well what do you think this is?
- 那只是用来紧急求救的 - 你认为这个是干什么用的？
I don't see a fire.
我没看见火
I don't see a gas leak, or flooding.
也没看见煤气泄漏 或者洪水
I don't see you writhing on the floor in the throws of a heart attack
我没看见你疼的在地上打滚
But God knows right now I'd like to!
那我就没理由打电话了！
She's gonna die in there and she's probably innocent!
她马上就要死里面  她很可能是无辜的！
None of them are innocent!
他们没有谁是无辜的！
You read the files. You know what kind of people end up in there!
你读了这些档案 你知道什么样的人才送到这里受刑！
Exactly! All we know is what we read in the files...
事实上！我们所知道的 也只是从这些文件上
Oh my God...
噢 老天
What if it's all bogus? The files, the crimes, everything.
如果这些都是在造假？ 文件 罪行 所有的一切
Maybe they're just putting anyone in there they don't like, maybe...
也许他们是被陷害进来的 也许
There's a purpose, and there's a plan.
有目的的 有计划的？
And I'm not so stupid to think that there's no plan just because I don't understand it!
我还没蠢到不知道这是个阴谋！
Here's a newsflash: We're just the button men!
最重要的是: 我们只是个按按钮的！
If we're meant to be analysts, we'd be working upstairs!
如果想要分析  那得是上头的工作！
Would you forget the party line for once and make the call?
难道你不能忘了我们的准则？ 快去打电话
Okay.
好
You do it. You're the hero.
你去打电话 当你的英雄去吧
Just remember,
不过你要记住
She was in the news and they made her disappear.
她出现在新闻里 还有是上头的人想让她消失的
How much easier would it be to get to you.
你太容易被影响了
No one even know you exist.
没有人知道你的存在
Who knows where you'll wake up tomorrow?
谁知道你明天在哪醒来？
Hello?
喂？
It's for you.
找你的
Yeah?
嗯？
Sir.
长官
Yes, sir. Right away, sir.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
马上 长官
I understand, sir. Yes, sir.
我明白 长官 是 长官
We've got work to do. Someone's at the exit.
我们有工作要做 有人到出口了
Our exit? What do we do?
出口？ 我们该怎么做？
The exit procedure.
退出程序
Wait a minute. I've never done this before. Don't you usually do this with Owen?
等等 我从来没干过这个 你经常和欧文这样做吗？
That's right my friend, but Owen is not here, is he?
是的 但是他现在不在这里
And the rules clearly state
但是规则明确规定
that two senior technicians have to be present
必须有两名高级技师操作
at all exit procedures.
才能全部退出程序
Right, but I'm not a senior technician.
是的 但是我不是高级技师
Hey! I need help here. That was a phone call from upstairs.
嘿！我需要帮忙 但是上面打电话来
Personal contact. Direct orders from above. They never do that.
而且直接下达命令 他们也从没这么做过
We can't screw this up.
我们不能搞砸了
- We? - Yes. We.
- 我们？ - 是的 就是我们
As far as I understand, sir,
伙计 据我所知
only senior techs are allowed to perform the exit procedure.
只有高级技师才能执行脱离程序
Perhaps it would be my be interest to abstain until receiving
可能这个需要等待接受
clearance from higher up.
上面高官的批示
You little prick.
你这小杂种
Okay.
好的
Okay, I get it.
好的 我懂了
Look, you help me with this, I'll tell them about your girlfriend. Okay?
听着 你帮我弄这个  我会告诉他们关于那个女的事情 怎么样？
- When? - What?
- 什么时候？ - 什么？
When will you let them know?
你什么时候让他们知道？
As soon as we're done with this. All right?
我们做完了就去 这样可以了吧？
Okay.
好
- What do I do? - Just follow my lead.
- 那我做什么？ - 我叫你做什么你就做什么
Okay, here we go. Step one,
好的 我们开始吧 第一步
Visual confirmation of subject in exit room.
视觉确认目标在出口房间
Oh, no. Owen.
哦 不 欧文
- It's Owen. - Shut up.
- 那是欧文 - 闭嘴
Hello?
喂？
有人吗？
Hello!
喂！
Anyone there?
有人吗？
Hello?
喂？
What now?
这怎么回事？
Please!
请！
Question one. Please state your name.
问题一: 请说出你的名字
Huh?
嗯？
Who are you?
你是谁？
He doesn't recognise your voice. They fried his brain.
他没认出你的声音 他们给他洗脑了
Please state your name.
请说出你的名字
- They fried his brain like the rest. - Shut up!
- 他们给他洗脑了 - 闭嘴！
I think it's Owen.
我应该叫欧文
Thank you.
谢谢
Question two:
问题二:
Do you believe in God?
你相信有上帝存在吗？
What?
什么？
Question two: Do you believe in God?
问题二: 你相信有上帝存在吗？
What is this? Screw you!
这是什么意思？ 操你！
Please answer Yes or No.
请回答是或者不
What kind of god would do this to people?
什么样的上帝会对人这样？
Please answer Yes or No.
请回答是或者不
No.
不
Okay?
可以了吗？
No!
不！
Now let me go. Let me go!
让我走 让我走！
God dammit. Let me out of here!
操他妈的上帝 让我走！
Hit it.
按下去
I need a doctor.
我需要医生
- What does it do? - Just hit it.
- 会发生什么事？ - 你只管按
Please!
求你了！
For Christ's sake!
一切为了上帝！
Still want your girlfriend to sail through to the exit?
还想叫你那个女的到出口吗？
He...
他
He's gone. It's over.
他死了 结束了
- He was one of us. - No.
- 他是我们其中一员 - 不
Once inside, he's one of them.
一旦进去了 就属于里面的人了
So this is your big exit procedure?
那么这就是你的退出程序？
What are we doing here?
你在这干什么？
"Do you believe in God?" It all hinges on that?
"你相信神的存在吗？" 就以这个为凭据？
I just read the questions and push the buttons, okay?
我只是读下问题 然后按下按钮 就这样而已
What happens if you push Yes?
如果按"是"会怎么样？
I don't know.
我不知道
No one's ever said Yes.
没有人说过"是"
Here.
拿着
Send this upstairs.
送到上面去
Do it!
快点！
Do you believe in God?
你相信神的存在吗？
What kind of animals would do this?
真是禽兽所为
Owen is... Owen is probably out sick again.
欧文是    欧文可能又去外面吐了
- You sure? - Yes.
- 你确定？ - 是
What are you doing? You're not allowed in there.
你在干什么？ 你不允许进去
I'm through pushing buttons.
我要按下这个电钮
No!
不！
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
白痴！ 白痴！ 白痴！
I'm inside.
我终于进来了
Okay...
好的
Thank God.
谢天谢地
You stupid jackass!
你这个傻瓜！
Good evening, Mr. Dodd.
晚上好 杜德
I believe these belong to you.
我认为这个是你的
Well, it looks that you got yourself a little bit of a situation down here.
看上去你好像碰到了点麻烦
May we?
我能进去看看吗？
The boys upstairs felt you could perhaps use a hand,
上面的人认为你碰到了点问题
and so, here we are.
于是我们就来了
My name is Jax and these are my associates Mr. Finn and Mr. Quigley.
我叫杰克斯 这是我的助手费恩 还有奎克利
Right.
就我们三个
Gentleman, first things first, we locate our mouse.
先生 首要的事情就是： 先确定他的位置
He has no implant and so we have to do this the old fashioned way, I'm afraid.
他脑袋里没有植入芯片 那么我们只能采取老办法了
Mr. Quigley, run a visual check on all rooms, he couldn't have got far.
奎克利 开个窗口查找所有房间  他不会跑远的
Yes, Sir.
是的 长官
Mr. Finn, run a probability tree on his potential movements.
费恩 运行一个概率树调查 他可能活动的范围
- Let's have some contingency, shall we. - Right away, Sir.
- 我们应该快点 - 马上 长官
Excuse me, Mr. Jax.
打扰下 杰克斯先生
Excuse me, sir.
打扰下 长官
Yes Mr. Codd?
怎么了 古德先生？
It's Dodd, sir.
是杜德 长官
What do I do?
我该干什么？
- I'm sorry? - What do...?
- 不好意思 - 我要   ？
Yes I almost forgot I have your orders from upstairs.
我差点忘了上面给你的命令
It's a personal delivery.
这是私人信件
% # @ $ *    "
"Order number 7-9-3, bla, bla, bla, bla... "
"命令 7-9-3
"Commence standard series of needle tests on Rains group. "
"开始对蕾斯小组进行针对性标准测试 "
- You do know what that means? - Yes, sir.
- 你明白那是什么意思吗？ - 是的 长官
Of course, sir.
当然 长官
All in a day's work, sir. Right away, sir.
一天内可以完成 长官 马上 长官
Do us a tinsy favour and use Mr. Wynn's auxiliary monitor.
为了能做的更好 用卫恩的辅助监视器
We'll need the big guns here for our little mouse hunt.
我们必须去猎杀这些小动物
Of course, Sir. Anything I can do to help, sir...
当然 长官 我会尽力帮忙的 长官
That the spirit Mr. Modd, way to keep the world safe for democracy.
穆德 就是要有这种精神才能维护世界安全
- Have we got a visual yet? - Still working on it, Sir.
- 看到影象了吗？ - 还在查找 长官
Okay, K-G-K. Three odds.
好的  K-G-K 3层几率
M-A-Q
M-A-Q. Three odds.
3层几率
Safe. Like taking candy from a baby.
安全 看来很容易
A-Z-Z. A-Z-Z!
A-Z-Z A-Z-Z！
Got it.
明白了
I don't know why we bother with these things anymore.
真不明白我们还担心这些干什么
A-Z-Z.
A-Z-Z
It's the first time I've seen a Z.
这是我第一次看到 Z
- Do you think it means anything? - I don't know.
- 你知道它代表什么吗？ - 不知道
Ah, don't let the door close!
哦 别让门关上！
Dammit!
该死的！
She's gone.
她消失了
Got it.
找到了
Subject is isolated.
目标被分离
And now the tricky part.
现在是动作部分
Okay. You were last seen here.
好的 最后看到你是在这里
That was an hour ago.
已经过了一小时了
She should still be in the same coordinate.
她应该还在同一个屋子里
The rooms move. Do they have to?
- 房子能移动 - 怎么会这样？
She can't be that far.
她应该不会离得太远的
Yeah but if we veer too far off course looking for her we'll never find the edge.
如果要救她的话 我们永远也出不去
What do you suggest, killer? That we'll cut our loses?
你什么意思 凶手？ 我们要丢弃我们的队员？
Uh, Guys.
喂 伙计们
Are we sure this room is safe?
你们确定这个房间安全吗？
Maybe he just starved to death. God I'm hungry.
他可能是饿死的
- What are you doing? - We could use these.
- 你在干什么？ - 这些我们有用
- We have to keep moving. - We have to get back on track.
- 我们要继续走 - 我们要回到轨道上来
We've already chased our tails for an hour looking for her.
我已经浪费了一小时去找她了 那个拖后腿的
God! This headache is not going away...
靠！ 头又开始痛了
- Maybe it's that chip in your head. - What?
- 可能你脑袋里有一个芯片 - 什么意思？
It's true isn't it? I mean they now put bio-receivers in all you army boys.
难道不是吗？ 我是说他们将生物 接收器植入你们士兵的脑袋
Keeps you on a leash.
就用这个来控制
Lady you've got a hell of an imagination.
女士 你的太会想象了
Jackpot. It's her.
找到了！在这里
Dammit.
妈的
Is she all right?
她还好吗？
She's not moving.
她不能动了好像
Great.
好极了
Wake up.
嘿 醒一醒
Are you all right?
你还好吗？
Rise and shine...
太阳升起来了
Is she...?
她该不会   ？
There's a pulse.
脉搏还在跳
She's burning up.
她很虚弱
Can you hear me?
能听见我吗？
- Oh my God. - What happened to you?
- 哦 我的老天 - 你发生什么事了
Help...
快救我
I need a doctor.
我要医生
- Don't let her touch you! - Let go!
- 别让他碰你！ - 别管了！
- Watch it! - Oh my God!
- 我的天！ - 不要丢下我！
Don't leave me!
不要！
- You just... - I didn't mean to...
- 你刚刚    - 我不是故意的
She scratched and I...
她抓我
You put her out of her misery.
你使她脱离了苦海
My headache's gone.
我的头不痛了
Something's eating her.
好像有什么东西在吃她
A chemical or a virus.
是化学物质还是病毒？
We never checked this room for traps.
我们还不知道这房间安不安全呢
I could be in the air.
也许是这里的空气有问题
- Let's see your arm. - We've got to get outta here.
- 让我看看你的胳膊 - 我们要赶快离开这里
- Show me your arm. - He's right, we've gotta get outta here.
- 让我看看你的胳膊 - 他说得对 我们得快点离开
Your arm. Where she scratched you, Let's see it.
让我看看你被抓伤的胳膊
- Why, you think...? - Yes, I think!
- 为什么 难道你认为   ？ - 是的！
Fine! there, see? Nothing!
好吧！看 就是这了 没事！
Flesh wound.
新伤口而已
Sure.
是吗？
Nothing.
没事？
What do we do with him?
我们拿他怎么办？
What do you mean?
什么意思？
I think whatever was eating away at her, is spreading to him.
不管是什么吃了她 现在已经感染到他身上了
- Hey I'm still here! - Not for long!
- 嗨 我还没死呢！ - 就快了！
- I say we ditch him. - Screw you!
- 我想还是放弃他吧 - 你去死吧！
Just relax guys, nobody's ditching anyone.
放松各位 没有人会被抛弃的
Look at him.
你看看他
Oh my God.
哦 我的天
What?
什么？
Your face.
你的脸
Crap.
完蛋
Please don't leave me.
不要丢下我
This is horrible.
太恐怖了
You wanna baby-sit a dead man? Be my guest.
如果你要照顾一个死人 随你的便
Please. I'll do anything.
请不要这样 叫我做任何事都行
Anything?
任何事？
From now on, you test the rooms.
从现在起 房间都由你来试探
All of them.
每一间
Fine.
好吧
Well, we're not going down there.
看来下面我们是不能走了
No sense wasting a good boot.
没有必要浪费一只鞋了
Help me!
快帮忙！
He's still alive down there!
他还活着呢！
Forget it, he's gone.
忘了他吧 反正都是死
You heartless son of a bitch!
你真是冷血动物！
No!
不！
- Don't come near me. - I was protecting us.
- 离我远点 - 我在保护我们
- You murdered him. - He was infected.
- 你杀了他 - 它被感染了
You saw it, it was spreading. We'd be dead by now.
你看到了 那东西会传染 若不这样我们已经死了
- You don't know that. - Actually, he's right.
- 你怎么知道？ - 没错 他说得对
It's a highly contagious form of a virus.
那是一种高传染性的病毒
- Flesh eating disease. - Who the hell are you?
- 嗜血病毒 - 你是谁？
I... I've come to help.
我    我是来帮助你们的
- Damn. - Problem, Mr. Scrod?
- 该死的 - 有什么问题吗？
- No problem Sir. - Anything of interest?
- 没有 先生 - 什么有趣的东西？
Actually Sir, I was about to...
其实 先生  我想要
Would you care to share with the rest of the class?
你会好好配合我吗？
Yes Sir.
是的
As I was running my test series as instructed Sir,
我遵照你的命令进行测试 长官
The query intersected with my subject, Sir.
这些结果是我从目标上找出来的 长官
Good work, Rod.
干的好 罗德
Who says they only hire the mentally challenged down here?
谁说他们只是受到精神的挑战？
Open.
张开
- Thank you, Sir. - Up on the main monitor now, Please.
- 谢谢 长官 - 现在请转到主屏幕
We keep... They, collect data and run tests.
我们收集数据还有进行测试
All kinds of tests. Testing Chemical and Biological agents,
多种测试 测试多种化学和生物试剂
Measure brain activity, endurance, most of it I don't even understand.
测试大脑的活性 忍耐程度 但大部分我还没弄明白
And that's just what I see in my department.
这就是我在我的岗位所了解的
I hear about others who do different work.
据说还有其他人在做不同的工作
I even heard there are other facilities.
据说还有其他不同的设备
Cubes.
异次元杀阵
Christ.
我的天
I just heard rumours.
这可能只是传言
- Why can't we remember anything? - I don't know,
- 为什么我们都丧失了记忆？ - 我也不大清楚
I always assumed that it was so they could have a blank slate to work with.
我只是觉得他们已经给你们洗过脑
Blank slate?  Bastards, you've been using us as lab rats.
洗脑？　混蛋  你们把我们当成实验室的小白鼠
Hey man, not me.
嗨 不是我
I'm just the computer guy, system checks. Stuff like that.
我只是个技术工程师  做系统检查 做些材料
Oh yeah, you just followed orders.
你只是遵从命令罢了
Yeah.
也可以这么说
- You make me sick. - Look, you got it all wrong.
- 你让我觉得恶心 - 听着 你完全搞错了
- I hate my job. - You're job?
- 我讨厌我的工作 - 你的工作？
How can you do this to people.
你怎么能这样对待我们
It was your choice.
是你们自己选的
You volunteered, only you don't remember anymore.
是你们自愿的  只是你们都不记得了
At least that what they told us.
至少他们应该告诉我们的
And you believed them?
你相信那些人？
Well, yeah. I saw the consent forms. Except for yours!
其实 我看了协议书 没有你的！
You're lying!
你说谎！
Who would volunteer for this?
谁会愿意来作自愿者？
Well it was either this or execution so...
实际上这也是一种酷刑
What?
什么？
They say you're all condemned prisoners,
他们说你们都是囚犯
who volunteer for the experiment instead of facing the death penalty.
自愿做这个的试验来代替死刑
I never did anything to deserve this.
我没做错事 不应有这种下场
Yeah well, tell it to Meyerhold, Right?
你去跟阎王说吧？
- We're innocent, dammit! - I didn't volunteer for this!
- 我们无罪 混蛋！ - 我不会自愿做这个的！
I know, because your consent form is missing!
我知道 因为你的协议书不见了！
Shut up!
闭嘴！
While you were doing your system checks,
在你检查系统的时候
did you happen to see a little girl?
有没有看见一个小女孩？
No. Yes.
是的 应该是
I mean, I saw her.
我是说我看见她了
I saw one little girl...
我看一个小女孩
In your dreams.
在你的梦里
- What? - Yeah.
- 什么？ - 是的
It's hard to explain.
这很难解释得清楚
Here.
对了 这个东西
You see, another thing they have us do, is record the subject's,
你看 另外一件他们叫我们做的是：
the people's dreams.
就是记录目标人物的梦
Her name's Anna, Right?
她叫安娜 是吗？
- They can see into our dreams? - Yeah.
- 他们可以看我们的梦？ - 是的
Where is my daughter, you piece of shit?!
我女儿在哪 你这混蛋？！
- I don't know! - You're lying!
- 我真的不知道！ - 你撒谎！
No, Please! I came to help!
请不要这样！我是来帮你们的！
Rains!
蕾斯！
We need him.
我们需要他
- Why? - I can show you the exits.
- 为什么？ - 我可以带你们到出口
Go ahead, where are they?
快起来 出口在哪？
You were wrong about the cube.
你们把异次元阵列理解错了
It's only 25 rooms all around.
这里只有25个房间
Only 2 rooms have Z coordinates valued 26.
只有2个房间有Z坐标标记着26
They periodically move to the perimeter,
它们是周期性的移动到边缘
but those 2 exit points are monitored.
但有2个出口点被监视着
And there's supposed to be an auxiliary exit.
但这里有一个意外的出口
That leads directly outside the cube.
可以直接到达异次元阵列外面
How do we get to that one?
我们怎么才能到那？
I don't know.
我也不知道
So what use is he?
那么他有什么用？
- Can you show us how to avoid the traps? - Yes, definitely.
- 你知道怎么检测陷阱吗？ - 没问题
Okay.
好了
Just read me the coordinates from the surrounding rooms, please.
请告诉我周围房间的坐标
I was right. The coordinates.
看来我是对的
Well, well...
很好 很好
It seems that our little mouse, is a rat after all.
在怎么说你们还是我们的小白鼠
Mr. Finn, could you do something about that, please?
费恩 你可以做点什么了
Yes, Sir.
是的 长官
This one's C-F-P.
这边是C-F-P
The hell...?
怎么   ？
- Damn. - What is it?
- 该死的 - 怎么了？
- The letters. They just disappeared. - What?
- 字母自己消失了 - 什么？
They're all gone.
自己溶解了
They know I'm here.
他们知道我在这
- So now will be a good time to move. - Good idea. You first.
- 现在我们最好赶紧离开这房间 - 很好 你先
Okay.
好
I can't make any promises, but this should be the way.
我不能做任何保证  但可能是走这里
Mr. Quigley, could you isolate that quadrant for me please?
奎克利 你能把他们分离开吗？
Mr. Finn, show me the current trap configuration, "s'il vous plait".
费恩 告诉我当前的陷阱设置
"Merci".
谢了
Let's make their life a little more interesting, shall we?
我们可以让他们更好玩一点
Okay...
好的
Trapped. Sure looked easy from my desk.
有陷阱 从我工作室里看起来很容易
They trapped all the rooms around us. Now what?
他们把我们周围房间的陷阱全部启动了 现在怎么办？
Really glad you showed up to help.
很高兴你能来帮忙
My God. I'm actually starting to enjoy myself.
我越来越兴奋了
You know what? I think we should keep getting together and doing this more often.
我们应该一起进去的
God dammit.
他妈的
What?
什么？
Sir.
长官
Yes, Sir.
是 长官
是的
Sorry, Sir.
对不起 长官
Right away, Sir.
马上 长官
"Just finish it, you idiot."
赶紧结束这一切 笨蛋
Ungrateful cretins.
蠢猪
You didn't hear that.
你们没听见吗？
Okay gentleman, we have the word from on high.
各位 上面下命令了
It's time to blow this popsicle stand.
是时候干掉他们了 奎克利
- Mr. Quigley. - Sir?
- 奎克利 - 长官？
You heard the man. Just finish it.
马上结束这一切
Yes Sir.
是的 长官
Okay, let me think, let me think.
等等 让我想想  让我想想
What the... ?
我们应该    ？
Now what do we do?
怎么做？
The floor. the floor.
地板 地板
I'm sorry.
对不起
God dammit! I don't wanna die in here!
该死的！我不想死在这！
What's happening?
怎么回事？
What stopped it?
怎么停了？
I don't know.
不知道
Come on, you piece of...
快点
- What the hell? - I don't know Sir, we suddenly lost contact.
- 他妈的怎么回事？ - 我不知道长官 突然连接中断
Yes, I can see that. Why?
我也知道 为什么？
Maybe the energy required for the test itself blew out the capacitor.
可能是因为测试能源 低于电容器所需要能量
I mean, we're not talking state-of-the-art equipment.
我是说不应该这样子的
Wrong. That's not how it works. That's not how it was designed.
错了 正常情况下是不会这样的
Someone is screwing with the connection.
是什么人中断了它
I don't know Sir. It isn't me.
我不知道长官 不是我
Me neither, Sir.
也不是我
What? I have no idea.
什么 我也不知道
It's not me, I swear.
绝对不是我 我发誓
You wouldn't lie to me, Now would you Mr. Clodd?
不要对我撒谎  克莱德你会吗？
No Sir. Wouldn't think of it.
不会长官 你多心了
Questions? Comments? What are we waiting for?
找答案和原因？ 你们在等什么？
Get us back online!
重新连接！
Damn.
妈的
- Nothing. - "Nothing" is not an answer.
- 不行 - "不行"不是答案
Excuse me, Sir.
打扰下 长官
- Excuse me? - What is it?
- 打扰下？ - 怎么了？
Can I use the facilities, Sir?
我可以用工具吗 长官？
Just go!
快去！
For the love of God, where do they find these people?
上帝 他们是怎么找到这种人的？
I don't think it's software, Sir.
我想不是软件的问题
- It's definitely a hardware problem. - Listen.
- 确定不是硬件问题 - 听着
This is getting embarrassing now. Okay?
这种情况很让人尴尬 懂吗？
I needn't remind you Gentlemen, that in a few minutes
我必须提醒你们  再过几分钟
we'll have no choice but to send people in there.
我们没有办法 只能再送几个人进去
Call me impulsive but I could probably think of a couple of names:
可能我会推荐两个名字：
Quigley! Finn!
奎克利和费恩！
You know, right of the top. What is that noise?!
你们应该明白 什么噪音？！
Something's wrong with the main power source.
主电源出了问题
It's gone into reset mode.
切换到重启状态
What the hell is going on?
妈的到底怎么回事？
Boot.
鞋子
- Damn. - You can say that again.
- 该死的 - 我也这样认为
What?
怎么了？
Power go out?
停电了？
Yeah.
是的
So the traps don't work.
那么陷阱就失效了
- That's the good news, yeah. - What's the bad news?
- 这是个好消息 - 那坏消息呢？
It's gone into reset mode.
切换到重启状态了
The system will restart itself in 10 minutes,
系统会自动重新启动 10分钟后
the first routine that runs on restart, is a clean sweep.
系统重启后第一件事 就是清空一切
- Is that as bad as it sounds? - The Clean sweep program flash-incinerates
- 那样很糟糕吗？ - 清空程序会在瞬间烧毁
anything still living in all the rooms.
所有残留在房间的东西
- So, we gotta move. - Which way do we go?
- 那么 我们得马上走了 - 走哪边？
I don't know.
我也不知道
Okay, last time I ran the numbers you were
我上次看见你们的时候
pretty much in the centre of the structure.
你们就在系统中心
So I guess we just keep going in the same direction
我猜一直朝着这个方向走
until we get to the edge, right?
应该就能到边缘 是吗？
Great, so we're back to square one!
那我们回到原来的位置！
- Do you have a better idea?! - No.
- 你还有好主意吗？！ - 没有
I don't. 'Cause I'm not the one who uses people as a fucking guinea pigs!
我没有 因为我不像有些人把人当猪一样耍！
Wait!
等等！
Back to square one!
回到原来位置！
Dodd. Dodd is the only one who can power down this quickly.
杜德是唯一能让电源这么快关闭的
But he knows that reset would kick in, so why would he...?
他知道重启会清空  那么他为什么   ？
Of course.
明白了
Clean sweep happens after they realign to zero position.
清空程序会让他们回到最初位置
- What? - Quick. Let me see your map.
- 什么？ - 让我看看你的图表
When the power comes on, the rooms are programmed
电力供应恢复以后 房间就会重新编程
to realign back to their original positions before the clean sweep starts.
回归到他们默认位置 在清空程序执行前
now, if we're in one of the exit room, Like A-Z-Z,
现在 如果我们在一个出口房间  例如A-Z-Z
it will move us to the perimeter, and
他会把我们带到边缘
we'll have about... 3 seconds to get out.
那我们会有   3秒钟时间逃跑
- Before it fries us. - Yeah.
- 在他烧死我们之前 - 是的
If that room hasn't moved, we'd might just make it. Yeah.
在那个房间移动之前 我们必须得赶到
You know Mr. Wod has been in the little boy's room an awfully long time.
伍德先生可能是在这里待太久了
Come on.
快点
Gotcha
成功了
A noble attempt to save your protégé, Mr. Dodd.
杜德先生你是想救你的朋友吗？
But quite foolish, ultimately.
但你这样做太傻了
May I have that widget back, please?
把零件给我 好吗？
I don't think I can do that, Sir.
我不会那么做 长官
Mr. Dodd, are you disobeying a direct order?
都德 你想违反命令？
Yes. There...
这就对了
Cute, and rather, cliché,
太好笑了
in an endearing kind of way.
这个办法还真不错
Unfortunately, I do believe there is penalty,
不幸的 我认为会你应该
a rather strict penalty,
得到点惩罚
for sabotaging state property.
罪名是破坏公共财物
Instant paralysis! They weren't kidding, were they.
马上见效 早该听我的就好
However, not to worry, Mr. Dodd,
不要担心 杜德先生
You still will be able to feel.
尽情享受吧
5 minutes to reset.
5分钟后重启
I think I found the source of our power problem.
我想我找到我们电力出错的原因了
Does anyone knows where this goes?
谁知道这个是用来干什么的？
Anyone?
谁知道？
That the central coupling. I got it, Sir.
是个连接器 我知道怎么弄 长官
Still doesn't solve our observation problem, they could be escaping as we speak.
还是不能解决问题 他们会趁我们说话的时候溜走
Sir, in less then 5 minutes from now the clean sweep kicks in,
五分钟后清空程序就要开始了 长官
and then I think our problem will evaporate.
到那时我们所有的问题都会解决了
Mr. Finn, I don't trust machines.
费恩先生 我不信任机器
I have a machine to thank for this, and this.
我感谢机器给我这个 还有这个
I need to see them, with my own God-given eye.
但我要用自己的眼睛看到他们才算数
Of course Sir, I just, I don't know how...
当然长官 我不知道
Sometimes I even amaze myself.
有时我都对我自己都感到惊讶
Mr. Finn, one of our runaway rats is a former squad soldier. Is he not?
费恩 那些老鼠中有一个曾经是我们的士兵  是吗？
Yes Sir, that would be Haskell, the big fellow.
是的长官 应该是海赛克那家伙
And they still bio-chip the enlisted men, do they not?
参军的人应该都有植入过芯片  是吗？
Of course. Sir, that's brilliant...
长官 你太聪明了
Mr. Quigley comes through.
奎克利搞定了
Mr. Finn, acquire us an uplink to the squad surveillance network.
费恩 我们把部队与监视网络连接起来
Yes Sir. Right away, Sir.
是长官 马上
- Time? - We still have 4 minutes!
- 时间？ - 我们只剩四分钟！
Hold on!
撑住！
There's no way he survived that.
他活不了多久了
We gotta go. Come on.
我们得走了 快
- We're locked on. - Sir, we have a visual.
- 锁定目标了 - 但是受到影响
It's a weak signal.
信号很弱
Your tax dollars hard at work.
你的薪水可能也会受到影响
Transmit the kill code.
调动谋杀指令
Pain inhibiters, activated.
激活疼痛抑制功能
Neuro-cam enhancers, amplified.
体力增强
- Are we there yet? - Almost.
- 我们到了吗？ - 差不多了
Haskell?
海赛克？
Move it!
快走！
Get off her!
放了他！
Thanks.
谢了
Okay, come on.
好了 快走吧
- How much further? - We're almost there.
- 还有多远？ - 就快到了
A-Z-Z. This is it!
A-Z-Z 就是这个！
It's okay.
幸好没事
The power's out. The power's out.
没电了
Chickliss...
查克斯
Oh man...
可怜的家伙
- There's over one minute! - Can't this thing go any faster?
- 还有一分钟！ - 这个房间还能再快点吗？
- Sir, we've got the grid display back. - They're at the perimeter.
- 可以看到了 长官 - 他们就在边缘
30 seconds to clean sweep.
30秒后开始清空
Well I think it's time for our little surprise.
应该给我们点惊喜
I hope your shortcut worked, Mr. Quigley.
我希望你能成功 奎克利
- Water. - The auxiliary exit.
- 水 - 另一个出口
Leads directly outside.
可以直接通向外面
- Now what? - Can you swim?
- 现在怎么办？ - 你会游泳吗？
Jump!
跳！
Well? Did we get them?
抓住到他们没？
Sorry Sir. The signal got scrambled at flash point.
对不起长官． 突然信号混乱 导致失败
I think we got 'em
不然就可以抓到他们了
I don't like it.
我不想听这个
Get a squad to the exit point.
派一个班的人马去出口
This way!
这边！
- Come on. - Run! Run!
- 快  - 跑！跑！
Go!
快走！
He's conscious.
他开始恢复意识了
Thank God. Well, welcome back Mr. Wynn.
谢天谢地 好的 欢迎回来卫恩
You're conscious. So, we can begin now.
你醒了 那么 我们可以开始了
"Eric Wynn,
艾瑞克．卫恩
"as you have been found guilty of high treason, sabotage
当你因为你的叛逃而内疚
"and various other crimes against your country and your God,
破坏和各种反对你的国家和上帝的罪行
"and so on, bla, bla, bla...
还有＃＄％％＃＠！＊＆
"Your sentence has been extended for two more lifetimes."
你的宣判惩罚将延续到你下一生
What sentence? I don't remember the trial!
什么判决？ 我也忘记是什么审判！
Well, you were found guilty. No further questions.
你只要感到内疚 不需要问其他的
Wait! What are you doing?
等等！你想干什么？
Well, we've decided on a few modifications
我们会做点小修改
before putting you back inside.
在放你进去之前
- Wait! - Mr. Wynn, you are holding up progress.
- 等等！ - 卫恩先生 你必须坦然面对
Don't I get a choice?
没有其他选择吗？
Don't all the condemned get a choice? I choose death!
不是惩罚都可以选择吗？ 我选择去死！
No, Mr. Wynn.
不 卫恩先生
You do not get a choice.
你没法做选择
You have already made your choice.
你已经选择了
I believe this is your signature?
相信这就是你的笔迹了？
- I don't understand. - "I don't understand".
- 我不明白 - 你不明白？
You chose to become a test subject. Many years ago.
你选择成为一个测试目标  就在几年前
And you simply don't remember that.
这么简单你都不记得了？
It's all standard procedure.
这是按照程序上写的
But my job? Dodd? Owen? Chickliss?
那我的工作呢？ 杜德？ 欧文？ 查克斯？
All lab rats. Just Like you.
都是实验室的白鼠 和你一样
Observing the observers, you know, that kind of thing.
这样是不是很有趣呢？
Very interesting results.
非常好玩
Wait!
等一下！
- You're actually starting to bore me now. - Where is she?
- 你现在让我很烦  - 她在哪？
Oh, the allusive Ms. Rains. Well, you needn't worry about her.
哦 你说蕾斯 你不用担心她
You didn't catch her.
你们没抓到她
He's all yours.
他归你了
- Don't touch me. - Don't worry. This wont hurt.
- 别碰我 - 别担心 不会疼的
Wait!
等等！
Mommy, I'm cold. Why can't we have a fire?
妈咪 我很冷 为什么我们不生火？
Because the bad people might find us.
因为有坏人会发现我们
I have something to show you.
我给你看点东西
See. That's us.
看 这是我们
We're superheroes.
很厉害吧
These are very special because they were drawn by a very special person.
这是个很特别的人画的
Is he a superhero too?
他也很厉害吗？
Yes. Yes, he is.
是的 他是
What wrong with him?
他怎么了？
He doesn't seem to know we're here.
他好像不知道我们在这
This room is green.
这里是绿色的
Hi there.
嗨 这里
- This room is green. - Yes, It is.
- 这里是绿色的 - 是 是的
What is it, shock?
他怎么会抖？
I wanna go back to the blue room.
我想回到蓝色的房间
I think he's mentally handicapped.
我想他是个精神病人
- That's all we need, a retard. - Don't!
- 我们最好都退后些 - 不要！
How the hell did he survive in here?
他是怎么在这里活下来的？
I wanna go back.
我想回去
Back. Back.
回去 回去
I wanna go back.
我想回去
Wanna go back.